SYED ZUHAIR HOSSAIN: class shesh hoile keo record off kore diyo, ami xm dite jai
Andalib Rahman Shagoto: Asi
ABRAR SHAHRIAR ABEED: eije bhai ami
TANVIR RAHMAN: ji
Shahed Satter: can you share the link to the problem?
TANVIR RAHMAN: no
SHOWMICK KAR: na vaiya
SHOWMICK KAR: Vaiya CSES editorial nai eta problem :(
TANVIR RAHMAN: na
MD. SADMAN SAKIB: m er value ki vaiya? n?
Shahed Satter: can you show an example?
Shahed Satter: like different start and end values niye
Shahed Satter: yeah better
ARYAN RAHMAN: 8 35
SHOWMICK KAR: Ji vaiya
Andalib Rahman Shagoto: Ji
Shahed Satter: slack link?
TANVIR RAHMAN: slack e invitation dorkar
TANVIR RAHMAN: expired
ABRAR SHAHRIAR ABEED: bracuprogrammers.slack.com
ARYAN RAHMAN: Practice korte gele bujhbo bhaiya :p
Shahed Satter: contest ki time constrained?
Shahed Satter: practice contest *
SHOWMICK KAR: Bit manipulation er upor ekta class nile valo hoy vaiya
MD. SADMAN SAKIB: Thank you vaiya.